getthere.net 2012-11-13

# Privacy Policy

**Statement of Privacy Practices Regarding Traveler Information**

_Last modified:   Oct. 29, 2012_

GetThere L.P., a Delaware, United States limited partnership, recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personal information about travelers that we process in and store in our systems. This Privacy Statement describes the personal information that we collect, and how that information may be used or disclosed by us, and how to correct or change it.  Please note that we may update and amend this Privacy Statement from time to time.

**Safe Harbor**

GetThere adheres to the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Privacy Frameworks with respect to personal information about EU travelers that we receive in the United States, and has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

Neither this Privacy Statement, nor our participation in the Safe Harbor program, applies to any travel supplier, such as an airline, car rental company or hotel, nor do they apply to any individual traveler’s employer or travel agency (for purposes hereof, a “travel arranger”) that obtains travel procurement services from GetThere. We recommend that travelers review the privacy policies of their travel arrangers and of relevant travel suppliers. In addition, our participation in Safe Harbor does not apply to travelers in non-EU and non-Swiss jurisdictions.

**Information we Collect  
**

GetThere obtains personal information when an individual traveler or a travel arranger submits data to us. Personal information that we obtain generally includes: name, date of birth, gender, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card and payment information, travel and accommodation details, passport information, and special travel requests, such as a request for a wheelchair or a special meal.

**Use of Information**

GetThere uses personal information to process travel bookings, to provide travel arrangers with access to travel information, to make and change travel reservations, to perform billing and accounting functions related to the travel, to perform internal business processes (such as testing and quality assurance), to perform and provide reporting functions for travel arrangers, and to issue tickets and other travel-related documents on behalf of travelers.

GetThere may combine personal information with information we have previously collected or with information from third parties in order to provide a better experience and improve the quality of our services.

GetThere processes personal information on our servers, including those in the United States, and personal information may be passed to other countries whether or not those countries have different data security protections than those of an individual traveler’s home country. By providing personal information to us, an individual traveler, or a travel arranger on an individual traveler’s behalf, agrees that the information may be transferred and stored as described.

**Disclosure of Information**

GetThere discloses personal information to travel suppliers and travel arrangers, as well as to processors that act on their behalf, to carry out the activities described above and to help perform the underlying contracts with travel arrangers.

We may also disclose personal information to vendors that perform functions on our behalf, including suppliers of software development services, business processing service providers, contact center service providers, training service providers, and computer maintenance providers. We require that these vendors agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Statement and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

We may also process and disclose personal information as required by law, subpoena, or regulation; when requested by government or law enforcement authorities; for credit card processing, authentication, and fraud prevention; or as otherwise required or permitted by law.

We may also process and disclose personal information in the event of merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of GetThere’s assets, in which case personal information will be among the assets transferred to the buyer.

We do not sell personal information for purposes of allowing third parties to conduct direct marketing for their own products or services.

**Cookies**

GetThere uses certain cookies that allow us to serve you better and more efficiently.  For more information regarding cookies and how they can be managed, please visit our Cookies Policy.

**Non-Identifiable Data**

GetThere analyzes, uses, discloses, and otherwise processes statistical and other aggregate benchmark data in non-personally identifiable (i.e. de-personalized) form that GetThere obtains or generates in connection with its business. This data may be provided to travel suppliers and/or travel arrangers for their marketing, tracking and related business purposes.  This data is used to identify trends and other activities in the travel industry.

**Security and Integrity**

GetThere maintains reasonable measures to protect personal information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. GetThere also takes reasonable steps, to the extent reasonably possible in the context of our role as an intermediary, to keep personal information reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete and current.

**Retention**

GetThere retains personal information no longer than is necessary to comply with legal obligations and to fulfill legitimate business and compliance purposes.

**Information from Minors**

GetThere services are not intended for use by minors under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from any minor child under 13 years of age.

**Access Requests and Other Questions**

Travelers may direct any requests to access their own personal information, or any other privacy questions, to GetThere at [GTPrivacy@GetThere.com](mailto:GTPrivacy@GetThere.com). In practice, travelers may first wish to contact their travel arranger, as that might be the most efficient means of addressing any issues. GetThere retains the right to use reasonable measures to authenticate the identity of any traveler that requests access to their personal information or otherwise raises any questions concerning personal information.

If any European traveler experiences an issue regarding personal information that the European traveler cannot resolve directly with their travel arranger or GetThere, GetThere agrees to use the International Chamber of Commerce as its independent recourse mechanism.  All disputes shall be finally settled under the Rules of Arbitration of the International Chamber of Commerce by one or more arbitrators appointed in accordance with the said Rules.  The location of any in-person hearing will be Dallas, Texas, but GetThere also consents to any hearing being conducted by telephone or video conference.
